Guide to the Records of The New York Institute for the Humanities RG.37.4
New York University Archives
- Series III: Audio Recordings, 67170
  - Subseries B: 1/4 Inch Reels (3 3/4 IPS), 67143
    - Metropolitan Correctional Center Panel Discussion: Session II of the Architecture of Confinement Symposium, 12-Dec-79; cuid4290; 180860; 2 sound tape reels Approx 1 hour, 50 minutes (Box 74, Folder 21)
      Former ACLU director and fellow of New York Institute for the Humanities Aryeh Neier speaks first and acts as moderator. Paul Silver, the architect of the Metropolitan Correctional Center speaks next. Silver is followed by Alvin J. Bronstein, the founder and director of the National Prison Project. After Bronstein is Judge Morris Lasker, a federal district judge who was in the litigation concerning conditions in the Tombs. The last panelist to speak is Kenneth Schoen, a program office at the Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, who is speaking more from his role as the former Corrections Commissioner of Minnesota.
      Access copy available on 3 CDs: ACCESS 9:44 - ACCESS 9:46.
      This is the second of two panel discussions in the Architecture of Confinement Syposium. The first may be found in this series (Box 74, folder 18).
      Prisons.; Imprisonment; Architecture -- New York (State) -- New York.; Architecture |z United States |x History |y 20th century.; Architecture.; Construction and architecture.; Bender, Thomas; Neier, Aryeh, 1937-; Schoen, Kenneth; Lasker, Morris E.; Edna McConnell Clark Foundation; Minnesota. Department of Corrections; Manhattan Detention Complex (New York, N.Y.); Halls of Justice (New York, N.Y.); United States. Bureau of Prisons; Bronstein, Alvin J.
    - A James Lecture by Joseph Brodsky, 21-Nov-79; cuid4291; 180958; Brodsky, Joseph, 1940-1996; Approx. 90 minutes (Box 74, Folder 20, Box Access 2, Item 16A-16B)
      Russian American poet & essayist, Joseph Brodsky gives an untitled lecture that the introducer says will demonstrate why Brodsky had said "Not all James lectures are alike." Brodsky speaks mostly in Russian. Barry Rubin, a lecturer in the Slavic Languages department at Queens College reads Brodsky's poems in English, throughout the lecture.
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 2:16A & 16B.
      Audiotapes.; tape reels; Russian American Poetry
    - The Act of Censoring: Session I of the Censorship and Writers Conference, 1-Feb-80; cuid4292; 180924; 2 sound tape reels Approximately 2 hours (Box 74, Folder 23)
      Recording of the introduction to and the first session of the Writers and Censorship Conference hosted by the New York Institute for the Humanities on February 1-2, 1980. This first session took place on the evening of February 1, is lead by Bob Silvers and Aryeh Neier and deals with the act of censoring, itself. Richard Sennet introduces the theme of the conference (described below) and welcomes the leaders of the first session.
      This conference focuses on the question "What does censorship do in terms of the act of writing?" The premise of this two day conference is the complicated relationship between writer and censor and between writing and censorship. This involves discussion on how the two are not necessarily diametrically opposed. Questions of complicity between the two are explored, looking at how the writer may serve as his own censor, creating a grey area between the act of expression and the act of repression. Rather than formal presentations, each session was started by one or two people "put some ideas on the table" and then a general discussion among the participants.
      The conference comprised three sessions; an evening session on February 1, 1980 and then morning and afternoon sessions the following day. Session 1 (evening, 2/1/80) was lead by Bob Silvers Aryeh Neier discussing the act of censoring, itself. Session 2 (morning, 2/2/80) was lead by Arthur Miller and Dick Sennet, discussing cultural censorship. Miller focused on cultural censorship in China, while Sennet lead the discussion toward "etherial cultural censorship." Session 3 (afternoon, 2/2/80) was lead by Joseph Brodsky and touched on the ambiguities involved in self-censorship involved in the very act of creating.
      See names and subjects for a list of participants.
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 9:19 and ACCESS 9:20.
      Writing; Censorship; Sullivan, Rosemary, 1947-; Silvers, Robert B.; Sennett, Richard, 1943-; Rieff, David; Neier, Aryeh, 1937-; Navasky, Victor S.; Morrison, Toni; Sontag, Susan, 1933-2004; Škvorecký, Josef, 1924-2012; Shulan, Michael; Scammell, Michael; Hardwick, Elizabeth; Enzensberger, Hans Magnus; Kennerley, Karen; Wieseltier, Leon; Wästberg, Per; Miller, Arthur, 1915-2005; Morgenbesser, Sidney, 1921-2004; Arndt, Richard T., 1928-; Baritz, Loren, 1928-; Bernstein, Robert; Brodsky, Joseph, 1940-1996; Buch, Hans Christoph, 1944-; FitzGerald, Frances, 1940-; Gilman, Richard, 1923-2006; Eder, Richard; Leonard, John, 1939-2008
    - Cultural Censorship: Session II of the Censorship and Writers Conference, 2-Feb-80; cuid4293; 180960; 2 sound tape reels Approx. 2 hours (Box 74, Folder 26)
      Dick Sennet starts this discussion on cultural censorship using Jean-Jacques Rousseau's 1758 letter to Jean le Rond d'Alembert on the Theater as a jumping off point. Arthur Miller, who was scheduled to co-lead the discussion, is absent for reasons unknown.
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 9:21 and ACCESS 9:22
      Rousseau, Jean-Jacques, 1712-1778. Lettre sur les spectacles; Writing; Culture.; Theater.; Censorship; Morgenbesser, Sidney, 1921-2004; Morrison, Toni; Leonard, John, 1939-2008; Miller, Arthur, 1915-2005; Rieff, David; Scammell, Michael; Navasky, Victor S.; Neier, Aryeh, 1937-; Buch, Hans Christoph, 1944-; Brodsky, Joseph, 1940-1996; Gilman, Richard, 1923-2006; FitzGerald, Frances, 1940-; Arndt, Richard T., 1928-; Kennerley, Karen; Bernstein, Robert; Baritz, Loren, 1928-; Sullivan, Rosemary, 1947-; Wästberg, Per; Alembert, Jean Le Rond d', 1717-1783; Wieseltier, Leon; Rousseau, Jean-Jacques, 1712-1778; Sennett, Richard, 1943-; Eder, Richard; Hardwick, Elizabeth; Enzensberger, Hans Magnus; Sontag, Susan, 1933-2004; Silvers, Robert B.; Shulan, Michael; Škvorecký, Josef, 1924-2012
    - Self Censorship: Session III of the Censorship and Writers Conference, 2-Feb-80; cuid4294; 180961; 2 sound tape reels Approx. 1.75 hours (Box 74, Folder 27)
      Joseph Brodsky leads the final conference session, discussing the self-censorship involved in the act of creation.
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 9:23 and 9:24
      Writing; Censorship; Eder, Richard; Buch, Hans Christoph, 1944-; Kennerley, Karen; Hardwick, Elizabeth; Morrison, Toni; Morgenbesser, Sidney, 1921-2004; Scammell, Michael; Navasky, Victor S.; Shulan, Michael; Brodsky, Joseph, 1940-1996; Sennett, Richard, 1943-; Leonard, John, 1939-2008; Arndt, Richard T., 1928-; Sontag, Susan, 1933-2004; Wieseltier, Leon; Bernstein, Robert; Sullivan, Rosemary, 1947-; Škvorecký, Josef, 1924-2012; Wästberg, Per; FitzGerald, Frances, 1940-; Baritz, Loren, 1928-; Enzensberger, Hans Magnus; Gilman, Richard, 1923-2006; Neier, Aryeh, 1937-; Miller, Arthur, 1915-2005; Silvers, Robert B.; Rieff, David
    - "Revival of Narrative in Historical Writing" a Gallatin Lecture by Lawrence Stone, 20-Feb-80; cuid4295; 180963; 1 sound tape reels Approx. 52 minutes (Box 74, Folder 29)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 9:25.
      First lecture in the Spring 1980 Gallatin Lecture series. Author and Professor of History at Princeton University Lawrence Stone - gives a lecture on the revival of the narrative method in historical writing. Stone argues that there is a growing trend among a small but prominent group of contemporary historians who were noticeably shifting away from analytical to more narrative writing styles in their works.
      narrative structure; Writing history; Writing; Stone, Michael Thompson Lawrence, 1919-1999
    - "Pornography, Obscenity and Freedom: Part I" A James Lecture by Bernard Williams, 20-Mar-80; cuid4296; 180862; Williams, Bernard, 1929-2003; 1 sound tape reels Approx 32 minutes (Box 74, Folder 30, Box Access 2, Item 6)
      English moral philosopher Bernard Williams lectures on the relationship between pornography and freedom.
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 2:6
      tape reels; audiotapes; Pornography |z Great Britain.; Pornography.
    - "Pornography, Obscenity and Freedom: Part III" A James Lecture by Bernard Williams, 20-Mar-80; cuid4297; 180926; Williams, Bernard, 1929-2003; Approx. 32 minutes (Box 74, Folder 31, Box Access 2, Item 7)
      Access Copy available on CD: ACCESS 2:7
      Audiotapes.; tape reels; Pornography |z Great Britain.; Pornography.
    - "Pornography, Obscenity and Freedom: Part IV" A James Lecture by Bernard Williams (DEACCESSIONED - NO AUDIO), 20-Mar-80; cuid4298; 180927
    - Australian Poets I, 24-Apr-80; cuid4299; 180863; 1 sound tape reels 01:04:30; Box label: Humanities - 4/24/80 I, Australian Poets (Box 74, Folder 33)
      Symposium featuring three Australian poets: Vincent Buckley, David Malouf and Les Murray. Symposium is entitled English as the Language of World Literature." Discussion of English language and aboriginal poets/poetry and the impact of British culture, imperialism and colonialism on the poetry of Australia. Symposium continues on second tape (ref2382).
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 6:4
      Australia; Aboriginal Australians; Australia -- Civilization -- British influences; Aboriginal Australian poetry; Imperialism.; Imperialism in Literature; Poetry.; Australian poetry; Malouf, David, 1934-; Buckley, Vincent; Murray, Les A., 1938-
    - Australian Poets II, 24-Apr-80; cuid4300; 180864; 1 sound tape reels 24:57 (Box 74, Folder 34)
      This appears to be the second part of the symposium on Australian and Aboriginal poetry that is started in the previous tape (ref2381).
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 6:5
    - James Lecture: Stephen Spender, 23-Oct-80; cuid4301; 180928 (Box 74, Folder 35)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 2:1
    - "The Prince, The Actor and I: Culture by Histrionics" (Tape I), 30-Oct-80; cuid4302; 180929 (Box 75, Folder 36, Box Access 7, Item 1)
      Part of the "Culture and the Actor" Series, this lecture is conducted by author Roger Shattuck on October 30, 1980.
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 7:1.
      Shattuck, Roger
    - "The Prince, The Actor and I: Culture by Histrionics" (Tape II), 30-Oct-80; cuid4303; 180930 (Box 75, Folder 37, Box Access 7, Item 2)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 7:2
    - "The Polish Lesson" A James Lecture by Leszek Kołakowski, 18-Nov-80; cuid4304; 180931; Kołakowski, Leszek; Approx. 95 minutes (Box 74, Folder 38, Box Access 2, Item 21A-21B)
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 2:21A & 21B
      Lecture by Polish marxist philosopher and dissident in exile Leszek Kolakowski, entitled "The Polish Lesson". This lecture came at the height of the 1980 economic and political crisis in Poland as the Solidarity movement emerged to challenge the Soviet control over the Eastern Bloc. Kolakowski discusses the current crisis, as well as historic factors leading up to it.
      Q&A begins at 01:00:30 on disc 21A and continues on disc 21B which is all Q&A. Questions are quiet, but audible.
      Solidarity; Campaign in Solidarity with Workers in the Eastern Bloc; Poland; Communist countries; tape reels; Audiotapes.
    - "Acting In Everyday Life and Everyday Life in Acting" A James Lecture by Victor Turner, 19-Nov-80; cuid4305; 180893; Turner, Victor W. (Victor Witter), 1920-1983; Approx. 90 minutes (Box 74, Folder 39, Box Access 2, Item 22A-22B)
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 2:22A & 22B.
      University of Virginia, Professor of Anthropology, Victor Turner delivers lecture entitled, "Acting In Everyday Life and Everyday Life in Acting."
      Q&A Begins at 28:45 on Disc 22B.
      Acting.; Anthropology.; tape reels; Audiotapes.; Theater.
    - "Modernity vs Post-Modernity" A James Lecture by Jürgen Habermas:, 4-Mar-81; cuid4306; 180932; Habermas, Jürgen; Approx 75 minutes. (Box 74, Folder 40, Box Access 2, Item 20)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 2:20
      Lecture by German sociologist and philosopher, Jürgen Habermas on "Modernity vs. Post-Modernity."
      Audio a bit quiet.
      Modernism (Aesthetics); Postmodernism; Post-Modernity; Modern Civilization; tape reels; Audiotapes.
    - Vladimir Voinovich Lecture, 21-Apr-81; cuid4307; 180964; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Folder 41, Box Access 7, Item 5)
      Lecture by Vladimir Voinovich, introduced by Aryeh Neier. The lecture was given in Russian and translated into English by a woman from a translation firm.
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 7:5.
      Russia.; Voinovich, Vladimir, 1932-; Neier, Aryeh, 1937-
    - Gallatin Lecture: June Goodfield I, 23-Apr-1981; cuid4308; 180933; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Folder 42)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 6:54
      Goodfield, June (G. June), 1927-
    - Gallatin Lecture: June Goodfield II, 23-Apr-81; cuid4309; 180965; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Folder 43)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 6:55
    - Gallatin Lecture: Jane Kramer, 7-May-81; cuid4310; 180934; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Folder 44, Box Access 7, Item 3)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 7:3
    - De Tocqueville I, 11-May-1981; cuid4311; 180865; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Folder 45)
      Reel 1 of 2 from this event. Reels from this event are Box 75, Folders 45 & 46. There is also an audiocassette that recorded the sections of the event that took place while the 1/4" reel was being changed (Box 72, Folder 99).
      Access copy available on 4 CDs: ACCESS 6:6-6:9.
      This conference discusses what de Tocqueville said about america and de Tocqueville as philisophical analyst. As a nod to the structure of "American Democracy" the conference is in two parts, discussing issues from Volume I in the first part and issues from Volume II in the second. This being Part I, the discussion is tied to "specifically American issues and Institutions" as was Tocqueville's first volume of American Democracy. Panelists include Tom Bender, Daniel Rothman, Aryeh Neier, Frances Fitzgerald, and Bill Taylor.
    - De Tocqueville II, 11-May-1981; cuid4312; 180935; 1 sound tape reels 62:10 (Box 75, Folder 46, Box Access 7, Item 4)
      Reel 2 of 2 from this event. Reels from this event are Box 75, Folders 45 & 46. There is also an audiocassette that recorded the sections of the event that took place while the 1/4" reel was being changed (Box 72, Folder 99).
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 7:4
    - Panel Discussion with Cseslaw Miloscz I, 22-Sept-1981; cuid4313; 180866; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Folder 1)
      Tape 1 of 2 from this event. Tapes from this event are in Box 75, folders 1 & 2.
      This event was a panel discussion on politics and writing featuring Czesław Miłosz, Joseph Brodsky and Robert Silvers. This is the first of two tapes from this event. President Brademus gives brief introductory welcome. This is one of the first academic occassions Brademas participated in as NYU's 13th president.
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 6:10 and ACCESS 6:11.
      Politics and government.; Brademas, John, 1927-2016; Miłosz, Czesław; Brodsky, Joseph, 1940-1996; Silvers, Robert B.
    - Panel Discussion with Cseslaw Miloscz II, 22-Sept-1981; cuid4314; 180867; 1 sound tape reels 00:01:13 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      Tape 2 of 2 from this event. Tapes from this event are in Box 75, folders 1 & 2.
      This event was a panel discussion on politics and writing featuring Czesław Miłosz, Joseph Brodsky and Robert Silvers. This is the second of two tapes from this event. President Brademus gives brief introductory welcome. This is one of the first academic occassions Brademas participated in as NYU's 13th president.
      This is the very end of the symposium. The tape cuts out before the last question can be asked.
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 6:12
      Brademas, John, 1927-2016; Milosz, Czesław; Silvers, Robert B.; Brodsky, Joseph, 1940-1996
    - "Second Thoughts On Consistency" A James Lecture by Hans Magnus Enzensberger, 6-Oct-1981; cuid4315; 180936; Enzensberger, Hans Magnus; Approx. 60 minutes (Box 75, Folder 3, Box Access 2, Item 17)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 2:17.
      Transatlantic magazine "Godfather" Hans Magnus Enzensberger delivers lecture entitled "Second thought On Consistency, beginning with a discussion of black revolutionary Eldridge Cleaver and the maxim "you're part of the solution or you're part of the problem."
      Q&A begins at 50:19.
      tape reels; Audiotapes.; Cleaver, Eldridge, 1935-1998 -- History
    - Tom Bender - On Charles Beard I, 22-Jan-82; cuid4316; 180966; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Folder 4, Box Access 7, Item 6, Item 7)
      Tom Bender explores the activism of Charles Beard. Five Themes persist: 1. Beard's Activism (Industrial City) 2. Professionalizing Context of Social Science 3. Beard's involvement with the Bureau of Municipal Research. 4. City Planning Profession & Movement 5. Beard's different kinds of activism over time with his changing philosophy of history.
      Reel 1 of 4 from this event. Reels from this event are in Box 75, folders 4-7.
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 7:6 & ACCESS 7:7
      Bender, Thomas; Beard, Charles H.
    - Tom Bender - On Charles Beard II, 22-Jan-82; cuid4317; 180967; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Folder 5, Box Access 7, Item 8)
      Reel 2 of 4 from this event. Reels from this event are in Box 75, folders 4-7.
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 7:8
    - Tom Bender - On Charles Beard III, 22-Jan-82; cuid4318; 180968; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Folder 6, Box Access 7, Item 9, Item 10)
      Reel 3 of 4 from this event. Reels from this event are in Box 75, folders 4-7.
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 7:9 & ACCESS 7:10
    - Tom Bender - On Charles Beard IV, 22-Jan-82; cuid4319; 180969; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Folder 7, Box Access 7, Item 11)
      Reel 4 of 4 from this event. Reels from this event are in Box 75, folders 4-7.
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 7:11
    - Discussion with Lukas Foss: A "New American Music Series" Gallatin Lecture, 15-Apr-1982; cuid4320; 180868; 1 sound tape reels 55:29 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      Part of the 1982 Gallatin Lectures "New American Music Series," this is a discussion with musician Lukas Foss, focusing (at least early in the recording) on the popularity of musical minimalism. Foss opens it up to questions and a general discussion with the audience at about 06:45. Introduced by Richard Sennett.
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 6:13
      Sennett, Richard, 1943-; Foss, Lukas, 1922-2009
    - Discussion with Steve Reich: A "New American Music Series" Gallatin Lecture, 21-Apr-1982; cuid4321; 180869; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Folder 9)
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 6:14 & ACCESS 6:15
      Part of the 1982 Gallatin Lectures "New American Music Series," musician Steven Reich discusses the influence of West African, Balinese and other musical traditions on his own composition as well as that of Hebrew Cantillation. He plays (pre-recorded) pieces and discusses them. Introduced by Richard Sennett.
      A lunch was held after the lecture, during which Steve Reich discussed music theory and research with colleagues who had attended the lecture. It was recorded and is part of this collection (Box 69, Folder1).
      Percussion; Balinese (Indonesian people) -- Music; Gamelan; Cantillation; Music -- Africa, West; Music -- Ghana; Reich, Steve, 1936-; Sennett, Richard, 1943-
    - Discussion with Philip Glass: A "New American Music Series" Gallatin Lecture, 29-Apr-1982; cuid4322; 180870; 1 sound tape reels Approx. 90 minutes (Box 75, Folder 10)
      Access copies available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 6:16 and ACCESS 6:17.
      Part of the 1982 Gallatin Lectures "New American Music Series," composer Philip Glass discusses theater and his work and music in theater. Glass plays and discusses some of his works. Introduced by Richard Sennett.
      Glass, Philip; Sennett, Richard, 1943-
    - James Lecture: "Jorge Luis Borges in Conversation" I, 29-Sept-1982; cuid4323; 180871; Approx. 33 minutes (Box 75, Folder 11, Box Access 2, Item 18)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 2:18
      Conversation between Jorge Luis Borges,Louisa Valenzuela (distinguished Argentinian novelist), and Chairman of NYU's Department of Spanish and Portuguese Literature, Alexander Coleman.
      tape reels; Audiotapes.; Coleman, John Alexander; Valenzuela, Luisa, 1938-; Borges, Jorge Luis, 1899-1986
    - James Lecture: "Jorge Luis Borges in Conversation" II, 29-Sept-1982; cuid4324; 180872; Approx. 24 minutes (Box 75, Folder 12, Box Access 2, Item 19)
      Conversation between, Jorge Luis Borges,Louisa Valenzuela (distinguished Argentinian novelist), and Chairman of NYU's Department of Spanish and Portuguese Literature, Alexander Coleman.
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 2:19
    - Nadine Gordimer Humanities Lecture, 14-Oct-1982; cuid4325; 180873; 1 sound tape reels 01:05:24 (Box 75, Folder 13)
      Nadine Gordimer lectures. She is introduced by Edmund White.
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 6:56
      White, Edmund, 1940-; Gordimer, Nadine
    - Economic Rights. A Lecture by Amartya Sen, 15-Nov-1982; cuid4326; 180874; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Folder 14)
      This lecture on Economic Rights was conducted by Amartya Sen on November 15, 1982.
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 6:57 and ACCESS 6:58
      Sen, Amartya, 1933-
    - Sir Edmund Leach, 25-Feb-83; cuid4327; 180970; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Folder 15, Box Access 7, Item 12)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 7:12
      Leach, Edmund Ronald
    - Italo Calvino I, 30-Mar-83; cuid4328; 180972; 1 sound tape reels 32:04 (Box 75, Folder 17, Box Access 7, Item 14)
      Tape 1 of 2 from this event. Tapes from this event are in Box 75, folders 16 & 17.
      Italo Calvino discusses writing. (First tape of two from this event)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 7:14
      Calvino, Italo
    - Italo Calvino II, 30-Mar-83; cuid4329; 180971; 1 sound tape reels 17:11 (Box 75, Folder 16, Box Access 7, Item 13)
      Tape 2 of 2 from this event. Tapes from this event are in Box 75, folders 16 & 17.
      Italo Calvino discusses writing (second tape of two from this event.).
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 7:13
    - "Jakobsen as Structural Linguist and Slavist" A Lecture by Edward Stankiewicz:, 28-Apr-1983; cuid4330; 180937 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Roland Barthes Festival: Richard Howard and Marshall Blonsky "A Conversation on Residual Barthes." Herbert Blau "Barthes and Beckett" The Pensum and Punctum" - Tape II, 19-May-83; cuid4331; 180876 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Roland Barthes Fesitval: Richard Howard and Marshall Blonsky "A Conversation on Residual Barthes." Herbert Blau "Barthes and Beckett" The Pensum and Punctum" Tape II, 19-May-83; cuid4332; 180973 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Roland Barthes Festival: Domna Stanton "The Mater of the Text" Philippe Roger "Portrait of the Artist as 'Gide mangeant une poire" Lawrence Kritzman "Barthesian Free Play" Tape I, 19-May-83; cuid4333; 180877 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Roland Barthes Festival: Domna Stanton "The Mater of the Text" Philippe Roger "Portrait of the Artist as 'Gide mangeant une poire" Lawrence Kritzman "Barthesian Free Play" Tape II, 19-May-83; cuid4334; 180878 (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Auden Festival: Symposium on "Auden's Legacy" I, 20-Oct-83; cuid4335; 180974; 1 sound tape reels (Box 76, Folder 24, Box Access 7, Item 15, Item 16)